{
    "subject": "resource/Battle_of_Hattin",
    "predicate": "ontology/result",
    "object": "DecisiveAyyubidvictory",
    "human_readable": "The result of the Battle of Hattin was a Decisive Ayyubid victory.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9638130068778992,
            "question": "Was the Battle of Hattin a victory or a defeat for the Ayyubids?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8847971558570862,
            "question": "What was the outcome of the Battle of Hattin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7670325040817261,
            "question": "What does 'Decisive' mean in the context of the Battle of Hattin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6272760629653931,
            "question": "What strategies were employed by the Ayyubids during the Battle of Hattin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6256524324417114,
            "question": "Who won the Battle of Hattin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.569240927696228,
            "question": "Who were the opposing sides in the Battle of Hattin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5606689453125,
            "question": "Where did the Battle of Hattin occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5588542819023132,
            "question": "Can you describe the significance of the Battle of Hattin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5293440818786621,
            "question": "Were there any major consequences following the Battle of Hattin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36845341324806213,
            "question": "In what year did the Battle of Hattin take place?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The result of the Battle of Hattin was a Decisive Ayyubid victory.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2786_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any major consequences following the Battle of Hattin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2786_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the significance of the Battle of Hattin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2786_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did the Battle of Hattin occur?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2786_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2786_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2786_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2786_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2786_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2786_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2786_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2786_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2786_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2786_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2786_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The correct JSON response is:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that the Battle of Hattin resulted in a decisive victory for Saladin's (Ayyubid) forces, supporting the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}